NEIL JOSEPH PIUS MORAS Mississauga, ON, CANADA L4Z 1C6

Contact No. +1(647)809 3325 Email: neilmoras@gmail.com

Visa Status: Permanent Residence

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/neil-moras-577a96a5/CAREER OBJECTIVE

A Web Development Student combined with 5+ years of previous hotel management experience aiming to leverage my current academic experience, a proven knowledge of communication, strong team work skills, programming experience, and database design to successfully fill the Junior Web Developer role at Creative Circle. Frequently praised as hard-working amongst peers and colleagues, who can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES AND SKILLS

- Hands on knowledge and experience with Front-end and Back-end web Development (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, XML, ASP.NET, MySQL, PHP).
- Fundamental knowledge and experience with React, jQuery.

FEATURED ACADEMIC PROJECTS AT HUMBER COLLEGE

❖ Animation Project -Dragon Ball Z Semi Interactive Fighting Arena Technology: HTML, CSS

This semi interactive game is created in order to showcase the skills and learning by using only HTML and CSS animations.

Fighter Jets World - CRUD based Project

Technology: ASP.NET, C#

A unique app created as part the Passion Project where the admin can Create, Read, Update and Delete information to keep the app dynamically updated based on CMS approach.

❖ Shawarma Kings - Restaurant Website Team Project Technology: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

A Team project mainly focused on JavaScript functionality where a restaurant website was created using Vanilla JavaScript.

Ticketing System

Technology: PHP, XML

This project is created with a focus on XML, were XPath is used to manipulate XML DOM elements where a unique ticket is issued to the user to the client where the admin and client can send messages back and forth to solve the issue.

WORK EXPERIENCE

❖ Food & Beverage Supervisor

Novotel Sydney on Darling Harbor, Sydney, Australia October 2018-November 2019

❖ Food & Beverage Team Leader/Supervisor

Novotel Sydney on Darling Harbor, Sydney, Australia July 2017-October 2018

- Food & Beverage Outlet All Rounder: High Volume Ternary Restaurant (Breakfast, Lunch and Dinner service, In Room Dinning, Bar, Cafe)
- Managed Conference and Events Department catering from 10 to 500PAX
- Employee of the month for the entire hotel January 2016, October 2017 and February 2018.
- Provided proper training and follow up to newly hired team members as well as the existing tenured team.
- Assisted the management in hiring processes.
- Increased revenue over budget by anticipating and prioritizing customer needs while presenting quality service
- Responsible for schedules, payroll and inventory
- Liaison between Sales Team and Food and Beverage Manager

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Course: Web Development

Institution: Humber College of Applied Arts and Technology, Ontario, Can-

ada

Year: January 2021-Present

Graduation Year: November 2021

Course: Master of International Hotel Management

Institution: Blue Mountains International Hotel Management Institute, Syd-

ney, Australia.

University: Torrens University

Year: 2014-2016